## ZEYNEP BEYZA ÖZDEMİR

## Software Engineer

### **About Me**

I studied in software enginnering and gradauted from Manisa Celal Bayar University at (2017-2022) . For about 3 years, I have been developing mobile applications that offer special solutions to customers and managing these processes. I want to direct my career in the field of Web-Frontend. I am a fresh software engineer who can learn quickly, think, be disciplined and responsible, inclined to teamwork, willing to improve myself in leadership.

I want to add value to your company with my entrepreneurial, enthusiastic and energetic personality.

## Education

Manisa Celal Bayar University, Manisa

September 2017-2022 Software Engineer

September 2012-June-

Yenikent Ahmet Çiçek Anatolian Technical Vocational High School,Ankara

Computer Science / Database

# **Experience**

Sept 2020-... Cactus Yazılım § Bilişim Hizmetleri-Frontend Developer

Mobile Application Developer / Project Manager

Jan 2019-Jun 2019 Tutkal App-Intern

I took part as a mobile developer in the team that develops e-commerce application in java language with android studio at Tutkal App company.

Jun 2018-Sept 2018 MobCodes-Intern

I developed a mobile application with java language in the mobile application department.

## **Projects**

RoCoo, Frontend / Flutter- UI/UX Web Design Jan 2022

A mobile application for a logistics company in Germany that finds the shortest route and lists the addresses for drivers, consisting of packages belongs to their own region.

İhtiyaç Varsa, Frontend/ Flutter Dec 2022

It is an e-commerce application that I am developing in my spare time.

Denebi, Frontend / Flutter Sept 2021 applink: https://apps.apple.com/tr/app/denebi-harcad%C4%Blk%C3%A7a-kazan/idl597934927?l=tr

Animega, Frontend/Flutter Marc 2021 -

Animega is a platform for anime fans to meet each other and get the latest trends in the anime world. Play store:  $\frac{1}{2} \frac{1}{2} \frac{$ Agu 2021

Marc 2021 -Ara Gelsin, Frontend/ Flutter

r you can access contact information and view profiles of businesses Apr 2021

Fingum, Frontend/Flutter Oct 2020 -

Fingum is a new generation social media application where you can share stories and meet people around you at your location. Mar 2021

Marc 2020-

Qupo, Frontend/ Java

is an E-Commerce application to be published in Germany. Nov 2020

## References

Cactus Yazılım ve Bilişim Hizmetleri - Founder - Furkan Bahadır ÖZDEMİR

Email: furkanbahadirozdemir@gmail.com

Contact: 05524184348



#### CONTACT

Address: Ciğli/IZMIR

zynpbyza0@gmail.com

gitlab: @zeynepyildirim06

in/zeynepbeyzayildirim-ozdemir/

507-042-2729

#### BIRTHDAY

01.08.1998 / ANKARA

DRIVING LICENSE

B Class

#### SKILLS

•••• Project Management

•••• Mobile Development

•••• Dart/Flutter

React JS

•••• CSS

•••• REST API

••• HTML

#### LANGUAGE

English

### TRAININGS

Patika.dev-IYZICO Frontend Practicum

Udemy Ileri Flutter § Dart Udemy Uygulamalı C#

#### HOBBIES

Learn Language

**Painting** 

Travel